[
    {
        "id": "13025343",
        "question": "15:43\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n7\nSố câu chưa làm:\n13\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 8 #13025343\n Báo lỗi\nRewrite the following sentence without changing its meaning.\nThe exam question was so easy that all the students got it right.\n It \n that all the students got it right.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "was so easy"
    },
    {
        "id": "13025334",
        "question": "15:24\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n8\nSố câu chưa làm:\n12\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 9 #13025334\n Báo lỗi\nRewrite the following sentence without changing its meaning.\nThe furniture was so expensive that I couldn’t buy it.\n The furniture was too \n.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "expensive to buy"
    },
    {
        "id": "13025325",
        "question": "15:14\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n9\nSố câu chưa làm:\n11\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 10 #13025325\n Báo lỗi\nRewrite the following sentence without changing its meaning.\nThe actor is very popular. Everyone can easily recognize him.\n The actor is so \n recognize him.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "that"
    },
    {
        "id": "13025318",
        "question": "15:06\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n10\nSố câu chưa làm:\n10\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 11 #13025318\n Báo lỗi\nRewrite the following sentence without changing its meaning.\nYour daughter is too young to watch this kind of horror film.\n Your daughter is not \n of horror film.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "old enough to watch this kind"
    },
    {
        "id": "13025311",
        "question": "14:55\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n11\nSố câu chưa làm:\n9\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 12 #13025311\n Báo lỗi\nRewrite the following sentence without changing its meaning, using the word(s) given.\nThe coffee was very bitter. My wife couldn't drink it. (TOO)\n The coffee \n.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "was too bitter for my wife to drink"
    },
    {
        "id": "13025296",
        "question": "14:45\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n12\nSố câu chưa làm:\n8\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 13 #13025296\n Báo lỗi\nComplete the sentence so that it has a similar meaning to the original one.\nNo one could move the piano. It was very heavy. (SO)\n The piano was \n.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "so heavy that no one could move it"
    },
    {
        "id": "13025343",
        "question": "14:38\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n7\nSố câu chưa làm:\n13\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 8 #13025343\n Báo lỗi\nRewrite the following sentence without changing its meaning.\nThe exam question was so easy that all the students got it right.\n It \n that all the students got it right.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "was such an easy exam question"
    },
    {
        "id": "13025334",
        "question": "14:28\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n8\nSố câu chưa làm:\n12\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 9 #13025334\n Báo lỗi\nRewrite the following sentence without changing its meaning.\nThe furniture was so expensive that I couldn’t buy it.\n The furniture was too \n.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "expensive to buy"
    },
    {
        "id": "13025325",
        "question": "14:20\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n9\nSố câu chưa làm:\n11\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 10 #13025325\n Báo lỗi\nRewrite the following sentence without changing its meaning.\nThe actor is very popular. Everyone can easily recognize him.\n The actor is so \n recognize him.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "popular that everyone can easily"
    },
    {
        "id": "13025318",
        "question": "14:11\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n10\nSố câu chưa làm:\n10\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 11 #13025318\n Báo lỗi\nRewrite the following sentence without changing its meaning.\nYour daughter is too young to watch this kind of horror film.\n Your daughter is not \n of horror film.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "young enough to watch this kind"
    },
    {
        "id": "13025311",
        "question": "14:01\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n11\nSố câu chưa làm:\n9\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 12 #13025311\n Báo lỗi\nRewrite the following sentence without changing its meaning, using the word(s) given.\nThe coffee was very bitter. My wife couldn't drink it. (TOO)\n The coffee \n.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "was too bitter for my wife to drink"
    },
    {
        "id": "13025296",
        "question": "13:52\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n12\nSố câu chưa làm:\n8\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 13 #13025296\n Báo lỗi\nComplete the sentence so that it has a similar meaning to the original one.\nNo one could move the piano. It was very heavy. (SO)\n The piano was \n.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "so heavy that no one could move it"
    },
    {
        "id": "13025343",
        "question": "17:40\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n7\nSố câu chưa làm:\n13\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 8 #13025343\n Báo lỗi\nRewrite the following sentence without changing its meaning.\nThe exam question was so easy that all the students got it right.\n It \n that all the students got it right.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "was so easy"
    },
    {
        "id": "13025334",
        "question": "17:31\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n8\nSố câu chưa làm:\n12\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 9 #13025334\n Báo lỗi\nRewrite the following sentence without changing its meaning.\nThe furniture was so expensive that I couldn’t buy it.\n The furniture was too \n.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "expensive to buy"
    },
    {
        "id": "13025325",
        "question": "17:22\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n9\nSố câu chưa làm:\n11\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 10 #13025325\n Báo lỗi\nRewrite the following sentence without changing its meaning.\nThe actor is very popular. Everyone can easily recognize him.\n The actor is so \n recognize him.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "popular that everyone can easily"
    },
    {
        "id": "13025318",
        "question": "17:13\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n10\nSố câu chưa làm:\n10\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 11 #13025318\n Báo lỗi\nRewrite the following sentence without changing its meaning.\nYour daughter is too young to watch this kind of horror film.\n Your daughter is not \n of horror film.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "old enough to watch this kind"
    },
    {
        "id": "13025311",
        "question": "16:59\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n11\nSố câu chưa làm:\n9\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 12 #13025311\n Báo lỗi\nRewrite the following sentence without changing its meaning, using the word(s) given.\nThe coffee was very bitter. My wife couldn't drink it. (TOO)\n The coffee \n.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "was too bitter for my wife to drink"
    },
    {
        "id": "13025296",
        "question": "16:49\nGrammar: Mệnh đề trạng ngữ chỉ cách thức và kết quả (2)\n Nộp Bài\nPhiếu trả lời\nSố câu đã làm:\n12\nSố câu chưa làm:\n8\n1\n2\n3\n4\n5\n6\n7\n8\n9\n10\n11\n12\n13\n14\n15\n16\n17\n18\n19\n20\nChưa làm\nĐã làm\nCâu: 13 #13025296\n Báo lỗi\nComplete the sentence so that it has a similar meaning to the original one.\nNo one could move the piano. It was very heavy. (SO)\n The piano was \n.\nBỎ QUA",
        "answer": "so heavy that no one could move it"
    }
]